acewebdirectory.com 2017-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Ace Web Directory

Ace Web Directory Privacy Policy:

At Ace Web Directory, we completely understand and respect your concern regarding privacy. Your privacy is of extreme significance to us and we make every effort to ensure that the data collected from you is protected and secure.  It is however, important for us that you furnish information regarding yourself so as to help us understand you better and make the entire experience here at Ace Web Directory a truly enriching one.

Our Privacy Policy aims at informing or notifying you regarding the data required by us and also our policies related to sharing it with third parties for the better and effective functioning of the website. The Privacy Policy is subject to the various terms and conditions laid down on the website. This also includes the conditions related to the modifications or changes that the Privacy Policy and other policies may undergo from time to time as stated in the terms and conditions. Please do ensure that you are completely aware of the modifications and changes in the policies as it is continuously updated. Your use of Ace Web Directory would imply your acceptance of the existing terms and conditions and also the changes made therein from time to time. Our Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into, the Terms and Conditions.

Personal Information and Other Data We Collect:  

Submission

Ace Web Directory makes every attempt to ensure that the user experience here is both enriching and satisfying. For this we require that you, the user, takes care to ensure that the submit form is complete in all respects with personal information like your name, email id and also other details required by us. The data provided by the user is used for the purpose of providing the services requested.

We also manually collect data which includes information like the contact address, telephone/fax numbers, email id, facebook id, logo, twitter url, company details, linkedin id and also the products and services of the company for the creation of a detailed business listing. For any further information and changes, we may be contacted at info@acewebdirectory.com.

Uses of Information:

Profile

The data collected from the user is safely stored as log files. The data collected from the user is used to put together a detailed profile of the user. You can be sure that we do not share profile created with third parties. 

Log Files

Like most standard web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Communications from the Site:**

Special Offers and Updates

The website is updated on a regular basis regarding the latest services launched and also new special offers extended to our valuable users. With the privacy of the users being the highest priority for us, the choice of whether to receive the updates or otherwise is left entirely to the user. 

Service Announcements

In certain circumstances, which are extremely rare, for instance, the service of the website suspended for maintenance, we may have to inform the users through personal emails. In such cases, we do not provide the user the choice of opting out as such mails are not promotional in I nature.

Sharing:

Legal Disclaimer

The privacy of our users is our responsibility. Every care is taken to ensure the same. However, we may need to disclose personal information if and when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Third Party Intermediaries

We use 2Checkout for billing the users for all the services provided. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

**Security**

We take every precaution and care to protect and safeguard the information provided by our users. The data and information of any kind provided by our users via the website is both online and off-line.

**Links to Other Sites**

Ace Web Directory holds no responsibility and has absolutely no control over the websites that are linked to us and those that show up in the searches. These websites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Ace Web Directory assumes no responsibility or liability for any such action and you are requested to scrutinize the Privacy Policy of such websites and remove any cookies from your computer if you do have any concerns. 

Copyrights

All material and content on Ace Web Directory, including website content, logos, or any other information related to the website, and any and all other components are protected by intellectual property laws. You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit for any commercial purposes, any portion of the website, use of the site, or access to the site, without the express and prior written consent of Ace Web Directory in every single case.

Additional Information

Ace Web Directory reserves the right to make changes to the privacy policy at any point of time. It is thus, it is requested that you do make frequent checks to be ensure that you are up to date with the changes executed. 

Any questions or clarifications whatsoever related to the privacy policy may please be forwarded through our contact page.
